<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Himachal Guide</string>
    <string name="cover">Let Take a tour to 4 tourist attractions in India.;)</string>
    <string name="swipe">swipe>></string>
    <string name="swipel">swipe</string>
    <string name="Manali">Manali</string>
    <string name="mussorie">Mussorie</string>
    <string name="barot">barot</string>
    <string name="leh">leh</string>
    <string name="shimla">Shimla</string>

    <string name="church">1. Church</string>
    <string name="desc1">
        This is the second oldest church in North India, and also one of the most
        famous attractions in the town of Shimla. For those who are in pursuit of peace, this church
        is a paradise and a perfect place to spend some time alone. The best time to visit here is
        early in the morning or during the church prayer.\n\n
        Visiting Time: 8:00 am to 6:00 pm\n
        Best For: Architecture and history</string>
    <string name="jakhoo">2. Museum </string>
    <string name="desc2">This museum is amongst the top places to see in Shimla as it is Himachal’s
        own Madame Tussauds. Displaying life-sized wax figures of Indian and international icons,
        this place is an interesting spot to visit with family and even friends.\n\n
        Visiting Time: 10:00 am to 10:00 pm\n
        Best For: Wax figurines of famous characters like Harry Potter and Iron Man</string>
    <string name="museum">3. Jakhoo Temple</string>
    <string name="desc3">Believed to be the highest peak in Shimla, this hill is 8000 feet high and is a major
        tourist attraction in Shimla. This temple is a heaven for all the nature lovers and pilgrims
        who come to visit the historic 108 feet tall Hanuman statue at the Jakhoo temple. \n\n
        Visiting Time: 7:00 am to 8:00 pm.\n
        Best For: Trekking</string>


    <string name="solang">1. Solang Valley</string>
    <string name="desc4">Solang is a popular tourist hotspot that is famous for its scenic views,
        and venturesome activities like trekking in Manali.\n\n
        Location: Solang Valley, Manali, Himachal Pradesh\n
        Things To Do: Indulge in activities like cable car ride, helicopter ride,
        skiing, paragliding, trekking, and zorbing.</string>
    <string name="pass">2. Chandrakhani Pass</string>
    <string name="desc5">Leading to the pristine village of Malana, Chandrakhani Pass is one of the
        most exquisite places to visit in Manali in December. Travelers can opt for an adventurous
        trek to the Malana village\n\nTrek Difficulty: Moderate\n
        Starting Point: Naggar Village\n
        Ideal Duration: 3 Days</string>
    <string name="temple">3. Gauri Shankar Temple</string>
    <string name="desc6">Gauri Shankar Temple is another famous Hindu shrine dedicated to Lord Shiva.
        Located in close proximity to the famous Naggar Castle, this 12th century temple is one of
        the best places to see in Manali in December where travelers can relish the architectural
        marvels, and intricate carvings inside its premises.\n\n
        Location: Naggar Castle Rd, Naggar, Himachal Pradesh\n
        Timings:5:00 am to pm 12:00 pm and 4:00 to 9:00 pm</string>


    <string name="zanskar">1. Zanskar Valley – Amble Among The Giants</string>
    <string name="desc7">Without a doubt, Zanskar valley is one of the best places to visit in Leh
        Ladakh. It is amongst the most desolate places in the Himalayan range. The steep terrains
        covered with snow reflect the heavenly skies.\n\n
    Best Time to Visit: Zanskar is best visited between June to September when the road is clear of the snow.
    </string>
    <string name="kargil">2. Kargil </string>
    <string name="desc8">A trip to Leh Ladakh is incomplete without a visit to Kargil. This is the
        second largest town in Ladakh, situated on the banks of Indus River. It is a transit hub with
        roads leading to Leh, Padum (Zanskar) and Srinagar. Also, it is a haven for adventure
        enthusiasts as they can enjoy sports such as trekking and mountaineering.\n\n
        Best Time to visit: The summer season between May to July is the best time to visit Kargil
    </string>
    <string name="nubra">3. Nubra Valley- Desert Among The Snowy Hills</string>
    <string name="desc9">Featured as one of top 5 places in Ladakh, Nubra valley, a tri-armed valley
        towards the northeast. The sand dunes of the Nubra Valley offer the tourists Arabian Nights
        like experience. Nubra valley is one of the most famous tourist attractions in Leh Ladakh
        for its two-humped camels.\n\n
        Best time to visit: As per the climatic conditions, the best time to visit Nubra valley is during the autumn season</string>

    <string name="fish">1. Trout Fishing</string>
    <string name="trek">2. Trekking</string>
    <string name="camp">3. Nature Camping</string>
    <string name="desc10">Trout fishing is the most popular activity in Barot Valley and attracts a
        large number of anglers to this place. One has to take prior permission from the Trout farm
        office for indulging in this activity. </string>
    <string name="desc11">Barot to Kothi trek is a 13-kilometer trek passing through the cedar and
        pine forests with such serene surroundings that make travelers forget the complications of
        life and witness the true colours of nature.</string>
    <string name="desc12">Barot Valley camping is another major outdoor activity which tourists can
        indulge into. Thandi Golai camping site is situated 1.5 kilometers away from the main market
        of Barot. It feels like the most tranquil and undisturbed place.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
